Previous Next

### _Call Today: [1-866-581-4540](tel:1-866-581-4540)_

 Search

    * [In-The-Home +  
        Fall Detection](https://www.alert-1.com/content/fall-detection-technology/1390)
    * [On-the-Go Wristband +  
        Optional Fall Detection](https://www.alert-1.com/system/on-the-go-wristband)
    * [On-the-Go +  
        Optional Fall Detection](https://www.alert-1.com/system/mobile-medical-alert-system/2717)

* 

Previous Next

Alert1 Privacy Policy
=====================

This website is administered by AlertOne Services, LLC. Alert1 is committed to protecting the privacy of any personally identifiable information you share with us and to informing you about how we will use your personal data. Therefore, we encourage you to read this Privacy Policy carefully.

Information on Alert-1.com is gathered in two ways: (1) indirectly (for example, through our site's technology); and (2) directly (for example, when you provide information on various pages of Alert-1.com).

The Alert-1.com web site will send a "cookie," a small text file, to your computer. If you visit Alert-1.com to browse, read, or download information, we collect and store some "visitor information" from you, such as the name of the domain and host from which you access the Internet, the Internet Protocol (IP) address of the computer you are using, the date and time you access our Web Site, and the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our Web Site. We use this information to measure the traffic on our Web Site with Google analytics and to help us make our Web Site more useful. We may also use this information for retargeting, which is a form of online advertising that delivers specific ads to consumers based on their previous online actions through Google Adwords or Doubleclick for advertisers. We delete "visitor information" periodically. If you do not wish to receive cookies, please refer to the "Help" file of your Internet Browser to learn how to either block cookies or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. To opt out of Google Analytics for Display Advertisers or to opt out of customized Google Display Network ads, you may visit the [AdsPreferences Manager](https://adssettings.google.com/).

Additionally, we collect information through our Internet access logs. When you access Alert-1.com, your IP address is automatically collected and is placed in our Internet access logs.

We also collect information when you voluntarily submit it to us. There are portions of this Web site where we may need to collect personal information from you for a specific purpose, such as to provide you with information you request or to deliver emergency monitoring services to our subscribers. The information collected from you may include your name, address, phone numbers, date of birth, or e-mail address, as well as the names and phone numbers of personal emergency contacts. When we collect this type of information, we will notify you as to why we are asking for information and how this information will be used. We will not sell your information and we will not send you unsolicited email.

If you are an existing customer and want to update the Personally Identifiable Information that you have provided to us you may update or delete this information 24 hours a day by visiting [My Account](https://www.alert-1.com/my-account.aspx) or call Alert1 during business hours at [1-800-693-5433](tel:1-800-693-5433).

If you choose to use our “refer-a-friend to Alert1” option, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. This process will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to learn more about Alert1 medical alarm systems. Alert1 stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email, after which the names collected are removed from our database.

We may occasionally request information from you via surveys or contests. Your participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary. The information that we request typically includes your contact details. If you choose to participate, the information that you provide will be shared with the contest/survey sponsors to notify winners and award prizes. Survey information may also be used to monitor and improve the content and performance of the Site.

Alert1's Web site contains links to other sites such as news sources, partners and sales affiliates. The information practices of those websites are not covered by this privacy policy. We are not responsible for the privacy policies of websites to which the Site links. If you provide any information to such third parties, different rules regarding the collection and use of your personal information may apply.

You are entitled to have access to your information and to have it corrected if it is inaccurate. 

Please check this privacy policy periodically to stay informed of any changes.

×

#### **EXCITING NEWS!**

We are very pleased to announce that One Touch Medical Alert is now part of the Alert1 family!

All existing members have been seamlessly transitioned to Alert1. Please continue to press your emergency button to receive help 24/7.

Please direct any inquiries regarding your account or device to Alert1's Member Care team at [800-693-5433](tel:1-800-693-5433) x 2.

For new service, please call Alert1's New Member Specialists at [866-217-1012](tel:1-866-217-1012) x 1.

Never face an emergency alone. We look forward to serving you!

Toggle navigation

    * [In-The-Home +  
        Fall Detection](https://www.alert-1.com/content/fall-detection-technology/1390)
    * [On-the-Go Wristband +  
        Optional Fall Detection](https://www.alert-1.com/system/on-the-go-wristband)
    * [On-the-Go +  
        Optional Fall Detection](https://www.alert-1.com/system/mobile-medical-alert-system/2717)

Get the latest from Alert1.

Thanks! Check your inbox for the latest on Alert1.

* 1 Life Alert® is a registered trademark of Life Alert Emergency Response, Inc.

**Need a hand?**

To become a Member, please call our **Sales Team** at ([1-866-581-4540](tel:1-866-581-4540)) ext 1  
Monday - Friday from 9:00 AM – 8:30 PM E.T.  
Saturday from 9:00 AM – 5:30 PM E.T.

For current Members who need **Technical Support**, please call ([1-866-581-4540](tel:1-866-581-4540)) ext 3  
24/7

For current Members who need general assistance, please call **Member Care** at ([1-866-581-4540](tel:1-866-581-4540)) ext 2  
Monday - Saturday from 9:00 AM - 5:30 PM E.T.

[FAQ](https://www.alert-1.com/system/faq/208) [\[email protected\]](https://www.alert-1.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) [Call](tel:1-866-581-4540)

©1988-2024 AlertOne Services, LLC.

[Privacy & Terms](javascript:void(0);)
